<resources>
    <string name="app_name">trivia</string>
    <string name="correct">correct answer!</string>
    <string name="wrong">wrong answer:(</string>
    <string name="x1">In the popular Harry Potter series, what is Hermione Granger\'s middle name? </string>
    <string name="x2">Who is the author of the famous classic, \'A picture of Dorian Gray\'?</string>
    <string name="x3">Who was the first Non-European to win the Nobel Prize in Literature in 1913?</string>
    <string name="x4">JK Rowling wrote \'A Cuckoo\'s Calling\' under what pen name? </string>
    <string name="x5">\'The Raven\' is known to be the most famous work of the unconventional poet X. Which one of the following is another work of his?</string>
    <string name="x6">\'And miles to go before I sleep\' is a quote from which one these poets\' masterpiece?</string>
    <string name="x7">\'7 Khoon Maaf\' is a Bolllywood adaptation of a novel written by whom?</string>
    <string name="x8">Satyajit Ray\'s crime thriller series stars an amateur sleuth fondly called Feluda. What is Feluda\'s real name? </string>
    <string name="x9">The novel \'Fahrenheit 451\' depicts a society where which of the following is banned?</string>
    <string name="x10">Who gives the famous speech on the \'Quality of Mercy\' in William Shakespeare\'s \'The Merchant of Venice\'?</string>
    <string name="y1">Who is the first woman to win an Asian Games gold in 400 m run?</string>
    <string name="y2">How long are professional Golf tour players allotted per slot? </string>
    <string name="y3">India won its first Olympic Hockey gold in the year?</string>
    <string name="y4">In which year did Milka Singh win the first national title in 400m race? </string>
    <string name="y5">Who among the following is not associated with billiards?</string>
    <string name="y6">In which year were The Asian games  held in Delhi for the first time?</string>
    <string name="y7">In which Indian state did the game of Polo originate? </string>
    <string name="y8">Which country did Sachin Tendulkar initially play for?</string>
    <string name="y9">Where was the first ODI match played in India?</string>
    <string name="y10">In which of the following sports can you win a \'Davis Cup\'? </string>
    <string name="z1">Movement of cell against concentration gradient is called?</string>
    <string name="z2">Most fish do not sink in water because of the presence of I-Swim Bladder,II-Air Bladder,III-Air Sacs,IV-Air in spongy bones</string>
    <string name="z3">Plants absorb dissolved nitrates from soil and convert them into?</string>
    <string name="z4">One of the following is not a function of bones</string>
    <string name="z5">Plants absorb most part of water needed by them through their-</string>
    <string name="z6">Process of cell division can take place by?</string>
    <string name="z7">Most intelligent mammals on the planet are?</string>
    <string name="z8">Prokaryotic cells lack</string>
    <string name="z9">Photosynthesis takes place faster in </string>
    <string name="z10">Nucleus was first discovered in 1831 by?</string>

</resources>
